Mark Beznos | mark@mtechnic.me | https://mtechnic.me/



Profile

My goal is to gain experience in the information technology field, and apply what I have learned in practice to my studies and future employment opportunities

Skills & Achievements

- · Worked under pressure to achieve success
- · Developed, deployed, and released apps for Android on the Play Store
- Bilingual in Russian and English
- · Driven and highly motivated

• Effective team leader	
Microsoft Office	/////////
Microsoft Windows	/////////
Linux	/////////
GoLang	/////////
MacOS	////////
SQL	///////_
C#/.NET (WPF)	///////_
Visual Studio	///////_
Java (Android)	///////_
Data Science	//////
Docker & DevOps	//////
Embedded/ARM	//////
Digital Ocean/AWS	//////
Git/Hg	//////
Python	//////
HTML/CSS/JS	//////
Photoshop	/////

Windows Server

Networking

/////___

////____

Experience

Camp Counselor, Springfield JCC; Springfield, MA - Summer of 2013 to 2016

- Worked with first through six grade age groups
- Learned the skills necessary to leading & managing large groups of people
- · Took lead in directing many projects, including a quadcopter photoshoot of the campus

Robotics, East Longmeadow High School; East Longmeadow, MA - 2011 - 2015

- · Went to VEX World Championship in Anaheim, California twice
- Created a tool in C# to aid teams in creating code for their robots
- Developed a application over a year to help predict match outcomes
 - Used web scraping & XPath to parse robotics score site
 - · Processed CSV data from robotics site
 - Exported data to Postgres database
 - Coordinated Python & Golang backend phases for the data pipeline

Technician, CMDTech; East Longmeadow, MA - October 2014 to March 2015

- Helped setup & administrate Windows Server based networks
- Installed network security appliances
- · Preformed various administrative tasks
- · Worked on client sites and helped with telephone support

IT / CS Intern, Traveled Insured International; Glastonbury, CT - Summer of 2016

- Developed internal tools in C# with Windows Presentation Foundation
- · Worked with Active Directory, Exchange Server, SQL Server
- · Did internal help desk support

Projects

- · Built a match prediction data pipeline, backend, and front end for robotics
- Created a social network for community activism that used KnockoutJS and Golang
- Co-Developed a Android-based messaging platform for emoji-only messaging using GoLang, Postgres, Redis, and Java. The backend was stateless and fully scalable.
- · Was the lead programmer on a highly-advanced robotics autonomous system written in C that leveraged sensor fusion for unparalleled accuracy and speed.

Education

Wentworth Institute of Technology; Boston, MA - Computer Science, Class of 2019

- · September 2015 to present
- Member of Institute of Electrical & Electronic Engineers
- · Maintains 3.39 GPA
- · Going for a minor in applied mathematics
- Graduating in August of 2019

East Longmeadow High School; East Longmeadow, MA - Class of 2015

- Graduated with 4.2 GPA
- Honors & AP student
- Former member of Media Club & Robotics Club

References

Please contact me for references